University of Connecticut 1987.0011
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VII: Speeches, undated, 1977-1985
  - "Fourth William H. Conley Memorial lecture, Sacred Heart University, 1984 May 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1357)
  - "Remarks of JAD at Second Century Fund announcement, Old State House", 1984 March 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1358)
  - "Introduction of William O. Bailey, Second Century Fund Announcement, 1984 March 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1359)
  - "Welcoming remarks at Second Century Fund", 1984 March 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1360)
  - "Remarks of Governor William O'Neill, Second Century Fund announcement", 1984 March 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1361)
  - "Remarks of William O. Bailey, Second Century Fund announcement", 1984 March 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1362)
  - "Remarks at Council of Darien School Parents", 1984 March 28 (Box 37:, Folder 1363)
  - "Statement of JAD on the passing of Homer D. Babbidge", 1984 Mar ch28 (Box 37:, Folder 1364)
  - "Channel 3 editorial", 1984 April 4 (Box 37:, Folder 1365)
  - "Shaping Your Future Through Education", 1984 April 5 (Box 37:, Folder 1366)
  - "Remarks at CT High Tech Day", 1984 April 10 (Box 37:, Folder 1367)
  - "Testimony to Subcommittee on Labor, Health & Human Services and Education Committee on Appropriations, U.S. Senate", 1984 March 1 (Box 37:, Folder 1368)
  - "Accepting honorary award for Dr. Homer Babbidge, remarks at Spring Conference of CT Association for School Administrators", 1984 May 17 (Box 37:, Folder 1369)
  - "Remarks at conference sponsored by The Center for International Community Health Studies, UConn Health Center", 1984 May 18 (Box 37:, Folder 1370)
  - "Dedication of the Homer D. Babbidge Library", 1984 May 18 (Box 37:, Folder 1371)
  - "Third Annual Waterbury Boys' Club Humanitarian dinner, Holiday Seasons", 1984 May 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1372)
  - "Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Dental Services Research Scholars Program, annual meeting", 1984 May 22 - 23 (Box 37:, Folder 1373)
  - "Welcoming remarks, Annual meeting of the American Physical Society", 1984 May 30 (Box 37:, Folder 1374)
  - "Commencement address, The Williams School", 1984 June 2 (Box 37:, Folder 1375)
  - "Commencement address, Quinebaug Valley Community College", 1984 June 2 (Box 37:, Folder 1376)
  - "Commencement address, Hartford Graduate Center", 1984 June 3 (Box 37:, Folder 1377)
  - "AAGSB Seminar on Internationalizing the Business School curriculum", 1984 June 14 (Box 37:, Folder 1378)
  - "Second National Conferences on Issues Facing Black Administrators at Predominantly White Colleges and Universities", 1984 June 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1379)
  - "The 1984 Six State Conference of N.E. Vocational Educators for Agriculture", 1984 June 25 (Box 37:, Folder 1380)
  - "Summer Institute of the Gifted and Talented", 1984 July 17 (Box 37:, Folder 1381)
  - "Distribution of Federal Student Aid Funds, Rep. Simon's Proposal to Reauthorize the Higher Education Act", 1984 July 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1382)
  - "Annual Meeting of the CT Pomological Society", 1984 July 24 (Box 37:, Folder 1383)
  - "Eighth Biennial Conference on Chemical Education", 1984 August 5 (Box 37:, Folder 1384)
  - "Perceptions of the Presidency: Who's Got the Power? Who Cares?", 1984 Summer (Box 37:, Folder 1385)
  - "Sixth Annual National Conference on Inter-disciplinary Health Team Care", 1984 September 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1386)
  - "Dedication of the Charles E. Waring Laboratories of Chemistry", 1984 October 5 (Box 37:, Folder 1387)
  - "Remarks at presentation of a Travelers Grant to the CT Small Business Development Center", 1984 October 16 (Box 37:, Folder 1388)
  - "Michigan State University Board of Trustees", 1984 November 15 (Box 37:, Folder 1389)
  - "Greeting to the 1984 Annual Day of Pride", 1984 November 17 (Box 37:, Folder 1390)
  - "CT Council on Higher Education (CCHE)", 1984 December 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1391)
  - "Notes for the Morris S. Dunn Memorial lecture, New Britain General Hospital", 1984 December 12 (Box 37:, Folder 1392)
  - "Message from the President", 1983 January (Box 37:, Folder 1393)
  - "To members of the Community, AA History Week", 1983 January 26 (Box 37:, Folder 1394)
  - "Letter to the Editor", 1983 January 28 (Box 37:, Folder 1395)
  - "Welcome to the Brothers of Alpha Phi Alpha", 1983 February 9 (Box 37:, Folder 1396)
  - "Statement before the Joint Commission on Appropriations of the CT General Assembly", 1983 February 16 (Box 37:, Folder 1397)
  - "Note on Audrey Beck", 1983 March (Box 37:, Folder 1398)
  - "Statement of JAD", 1983 March 7 (Box 37:, Folder 1399)
  - "60th AADS Annual Session", 1983 March 15 (Box 37:, Folder 1400)
  - "Response of JAD to a WFSB editorial", 1983 March 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1401)
  - "Statement before the Joint Committee on Education", 1983 March 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1402)
  - "Puerto-Rican-Hispanic History Observance Month", 1983 March 30 (Box 37:, Folder 1403)
  - "Activities Orientation Handbook", 1983 April (Box 37:, Folder 1404)
  - "Senior prom", 1983 April 6 (Box 37:, Folder 1405)
  - "Remarks to the Mortar Board", 1983 April 10 (Box 37:, Folder 1406)
  - "NEAEOPP Seventh Annual Conference", 1983 April 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1407)
  - "To Members of the University Community re Piano Monster Concert", 1983 April 12 (Box 37:, Folder 1408)
  - "School of Fine Arts orientation", 1983 April 26 (Box 37:, Folder 1409)
  - "Remarks at CT High Tech Fair", 1983 April 28 (Box 37:, Folder 1410)
  - "Fourth Annual Conference, CT Association of Latins in Higher Education", 1983 April 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1411)
  - "Men's Club dinner", 1983 May 2 (Box 37:, Folder 1412)
  - "Testimony to the Subcommittee on Labor-HHS-Education Committee on Appropriations, U.S. Senate", 1983 May 3 (Box 37:, Folder 1413)
  - "Convocation, UConn Nursing", 1983 May 7 (Box 37:, Folder 1414)
  - "To CT Bar Association", 1983 May 24 (Box 37:, Folder 1415)
  - "Commencement address, Windsor High School", 1983 June 15 (Box 37:, Folder 1416)
  - "Statement re BOG", 1983 June 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1417)
  - "Tirozzi testimonial dinner", 1983 June 28 (Box 37:, Folder 1418)
  - "N.E. Congressional Caucus testimony", 1983 July 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1419)
  - "1983 legislative wrap-up", 1983 July 22 (Box 37:, Folder 1420)
  - "Remarks re Gifted and Talented institute '83", 1983 July 26 (Box 37:, Folder 1421)
  - "Statement for alumni fund-raising brochure", 1983 July 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1422)
  - "Freshman convocation", 1983 September 6 (Box 37:, Folder 1423)
  - "Message in Newsletter Publication by Technology Transfer Center", 1983 September 12 (Box 37:, Folder 1424)
  - "Opening concert of 1983-1984 season at Von der Mehden", 1983 September 13 (Box 37:, Folder 1425)
  - "Oral history workshop", 1983 September 24 (Box 37:, Folder 1426)
  - "Statement for Afro-American Cultural Center", 1983 September 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1427)
  - "Cooperative Extension Service, Homemaker's Recognition Day", 1983 October 1 (Box 37:, Folder 1428)
  - "World Food Day", 1983 October 7 (Box 37:, Folder 1429)
  - "University Library 5th birthday celebration", 1983 November 2 (Box 37:, Folder 1430)
  - "Shaping the Future Through Education, remarks at Hartford Rotary Club", 1983 November 7 (Box 37:, Folder 1431)
  - "Seminar/workshop for high school social studies Teachers", 1983 November 16 (Box 37:, Folder 1432)
  - "Conference on controlling health care costs", 1983 November 17 (Box 37:, Folder 1433)
  - "Day of Pride", 1983 November 19 (Box 37:, Folder 1434)
  - "Letter to the Editor", 1983 December 1 (Box 37:, Folder 1435)
  - "Flexner revisited", 1983 December 5 (Box 37:, Folder 1436)
  - "Remarks re Afro-American history observance", 1982 January 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1437)
  - "Public spending in CT", 1982 January 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1438)
  - "Channel 3 editorial statement", 1982 January 29; (2 versions) (Box 37:, Folder 1439)
  - "Afro-American History Observance Month", 1982 February 1 (Box 37:, Folder 1440)
  - "Preliminary comments, Report of the Governor's Commission on Higher Education and the Economy", 1982 February 10 (Box 37:, Folder 1441)
  - "Statement, Joint Committee on Appropriations of the General Assembly", 1982 February 10 (Box 37:, Folder 1442)
  - "Professional Turf and Landscapers" (Ground Keepers Association), 1982 February 18 (Box 37:, Folder 1443)
  - "Testimony, field hearing of the U.S. Senate Subcommittee on Education", 1982 February 19 (Box 37:, Folder 1444)
  - "CT Urban League", 1982 February 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1445)
  - "Letter to parents of University students", 1982 March 8 (Box 37:, Folder 1446)
  - "Letter to the Editor, CT Daily Campus", 1982 March 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1447)
  - "Combined Health Appeal", 1982 March 22 (Box 37:, Folder 1448)
  - "Letter to members of University community", 1982 March 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1449)
  - "Puerto Rican-Hispanic History Observance Month", 1982 March 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1450)
  - "Lions Club tree planting", 1982 April 18 (Box 37:, Folder 1451)
  - "CT colleges and corporations, Conference on Higher Education and CT Economy" (AAUP), 1982 April 27 (Box 37:, Folder 1452)
  - "Hartford County Medical Association", 1982 April 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1453)
  - "Letter to the Graduates", 1982 May (Box 37:, Folder 1454)
  - "Educational Policy Fellowship Program", 1982 May 3 (Box 37:, Folder 1455)
  - "Institute for Educational Leadership Convocation, School of Nursing", 1982 May 9 (Box 37:, Folder 1456)
  - "Commencement, Mohegan Community College", 1982 May 16 (Box 37:, Folder 1457)
  - "Auxiliary of American Cancer Society lunch", 1982 May 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1458)
  - "Unpatriotic" behavior, Russian Scientists, 1982 May 25 (Box 37:, Folder 1459)
  - "N.E. Regional Student Program, NEBHE Conference", 1982 May 26 (Box 37:, Folder 1460)
  - "UConn Alumni Awards dinner", 1982 May 28 (Box 37:, Folder 1461)
  - "Summary of legislation", 1982 June 1 (Box 37:, Folder 1462)
  - "Annual academic awards, Farmington High", 1982 June 2 (Box 37:, Folder 1463)
  - "Notes for mailing to alumni, et. al.", 1982 June 3 (Box 37:, Folder 1464)
  - "Urban Academy of New Haven Schools", 1982 June 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1465)
  - "Manger's Meeting, Department of Economic Dev.", 1982 July 15 (Box 37:, Folder 1466)
  - "Letter to Modern Greek Studies donors", 1982 August 23 (Box 37:, Folder 1467)
  - "Second Newsletter", 1982 September (Box 37:, Folder 1468)
  - "Letter to the alumni", 1982 September 3 (Box 37:, Folder 1469)
  - "Letter to the Editor", 1982 September 6 (Box 37:, Folder 1470)
  - "Freshman convocation, Class of 1986", 1982 September 8 (Box 37:, Folder 1471)
  - "Letter to the Editor, CDC", 1982 September 9 (Box 37:, Folder 1472)
  - "N.E. Association of School Superintendents, annual conference", 1982 September 19 (Box 37:, Folder 1473)
  - "CT Commission on the Arts, welcoming remarks", 1982 September 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1474)
  - "Day of Pride", 1982 October 4 (Box 37:, Folder 1475)
  - "Letter to members of the University community re bloodmobile", 1982 October 5 (Box 37:, Folder 1476)
  - "Valley District Dental Society", 1982 October 6 (Box 37:, Folder 1477)
  - "Parent's Day 1982", 1982 October 9 (Box 37:, Folder 1478)
  - "Response to WFSB editorial, 10/6/82", 1982 October 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1479)
  - "Response to WFSB editorial, 10/8/82", 1982 October 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1480)
  - "Letter to colleagues re United Way Campaign", 1982 October 15 (Box 37:, Folder 1481)
  - "Day of Pride 1982", 1982 October 17 (Box 37:, Folder 1482)
  - "Remarks at announcement of Hamilton Standard Division support for engineering programs", 1982 October 19 (Box 37:, Folder 1483)
  - "WFSB-TV, Channel 3 news 11:00 p.m.", 1982 October 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1484)
  - "CT State Grange", 1982 October 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1485)
  - "Remarks, Willimantic Rotary Club", 1982 October 26 (Box 37:, Folder 1486)
  - "Message from the President", 1982 November (Box 37:, Folder 1487)
  - "Letter re food donations", 1982 November 4 (Box 37:, Folder 1488)
  - "Alumni Association dinner for outstanding CT high school teachers", 1982 November 15 (Box 37:, Folder 1489)
  - "Remarks at opening of the Center for the Study of Public Policy", 1982 November 30 (Box 37:, Folder 1490)
  - "Message from the President, 2nd in series", 1982 November 30 (Box 37:, Folder 1491)
  - "Alumni Association's Legislator's Day", 1982 December 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1492)
  - "Remarks to the Alumni Association", 1981 January (Box 37:, Folder 1493)
  - "Search for Vice President Student Affairs, memo", 1981 January 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1494)
  - "CASE regional conference", 1981 January 27 (Box 37:, Folder 1495)
  - "Statement, Joint Committee on Appropriations, General Assembly", 1981 February 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1496)
  - "Alpha Phi Omega N.E. Sectional Conference", 1981 February 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1497)
  - "Notes, UConn League", 1981 February 23 (Box 37:, Folder 1498)
  - "Statement, Joint Committee on Education, General Assembly", 1981 March 2 (Box 37:, Folder 1499)
  - "Hartford Rotary Club", 1981 April 6 (Box 37:, Folder 1500)
  - "Centennial, Slavic Studies", 1981 April 10 (Box 37:, Folder 1501)
  - "N.E. 7 Regional Medical, Chemical, Immunology and Pharmaceutical Conference", 1981 April 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1502)
  - "Centennial convocation, School of Nursing", 1981 April 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1503)
  - "Centennial celebration, remarks of Andrew Canzonetti", 1981 April 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1504)
  - "Centennial celebration, remarks of JAD", 1981 April 21 (Box 37:, Folder 1505)
  - "Centennial Symposium on Health and Nutrition in CT", 1981 April 23 (Box 37:, Folder 1506)
  - "The Loeser Award, 1981 April 27 (Box 37:, Folder 1507)
  - "Juniper Hill Village dedication", 1981 May 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1508)
  - "Phi Lambda Theta remarks", 1981 May 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1509)
  - "Senior convocation, School of Nursing", 1981 May 10 (Box 38:, Folder 1510)
  - "Hartford insurance industry greetings", 1981 May 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1511)
  - "CT Association of School Administrators", 1981 May 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1512)
  - "Commencement, Fairleigh Dickinson University", 1981 May 17 (Box 38:, Folder 1513)
  - "Centennial symposium on computer technology and applications", 1981 May 19 (Box 38:, Folder 1514)
  - "Greater Hartford Alumni chapter", 1981 May 19 (Box 38:, Folder 1515)
  - "Response to inquiries, NWSA conferences", 1981 May 20 (Box 38:, Folder 1516)
  - "98th Commencement exercises", 1981 May 24 (Box 38:, Folder 1517)
  - "The McLean Home", 1981 May 28 (Box 38:, Folder 1518)
  - "Health Center centennial", 1981 May 29 (Box 38:, Folder 1519)
  - "Distinguished Alumni awards dinner", 1981 May 29 (Box 38:, Folder 1520)
  - "Commencement, Kingswood Oxford School", 1981 June 4 (Box 38:, Folder 1521)
  - "Commencement, Briarwood College", 1981 June 6 (Box 38:, Folder 1522)
  - "Sacred Heart University", 1981 June 22 (Box 38:, Folder 1523)
  - "Commencement address, E.O. Smith", 1981 June 25 (Box 38:, Folder 1524)
  - "Manchester "Old Guard" and Kiwanis", 1981 July 7 (Box 38:, Folder 1525)
  - "Innovation and Technology Subcommittee of the Senate Small Business Committee", 1981 July 8 (Box 38:, Folder 1526)
  - "Commission of Higher Education and Economy, Higher Education Daily", 1981 August 14 (Box 38:, Folder 1527)
  - "Freshman convocation, Class of '85", 1981 September 8 (Box 38:, Folder 1528)
  - "Partners with Tomorrow", film, 1981 September 8 (Box 38:, Folder 1529)
  - "Frontiers of the Future, introduction of Douglas Costly", 1981 September 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1530)
  - "Frontiers of the Future, Introduction of Arthur Schlesinger", 1981 September 16 (Box 38:, Folder 1531)
  - "Frontiers of the Future, Introduction of Isaac Asimov", 1981 September 17 (Box 38:, Folder 1532)
  - "Frontiers of the Future, Introduction of Suzanne Keller", 1981 September 17 (Box 38:, Folder 1533)
  - "Second Century convocation", 1981 September 19 (Box 38:, Folder 1534)
  - "Second Century convocation, remarks of Andrew Canzonetti", 1981 September 19 (Box 38:, Folder 1535)
  - "Radiology in Stratford on Avon", 1981 September 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1536)
  - "Convocation honoring retired members of the faculty and staff", 1981 October 4 (Box 38:, Folder 1537)
  - "Excerpts, Governor's Blue Ribbon Committee on Higher Education and Economy", 1981 October 13 (Box 38:, Folder 1538)
  - "Remarks, Governor's Blue Ribbon Committee Frank D. Rich", 1981 October 13 (Box 38:, Folder 1539)
  - "Testimony, House Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education", 1981 October 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1540)
  - "CT Academy of Family Physicians", 1981 October 21 (Box 38:, Folder 1541)
  - "Introduction, Pennsylvania", 1981 October 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1542)
  - "Samuel and Hilda Shames lecture", 1981 October 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1543)
  - "Remarks, Physics", 1981 October 28 (Box 38:, Folder 1544)
  - "South Windsor schools", 1981 October 30 (Box 38:, Folder 1545)
  - "AAUP remarks", 1981 October 30 (Box 38:, Folder 1546)
  - "Day of Pride", 1981 October 31 (Box 38:, Folder 1547)
  - "Connecticut Nurseryman Association, annual meeting", 1980 January 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1548)
  - "Presentation to the Office of Residential Life", 1980 January 17 (Box 38:, Folder 1549)
  - "N.E. Pharmacologists, 9th meeting welcoming Remarks", 1980 January 25 (Box 38:, Folder 1550)
  - "Statement re Alpha Phi Alpha fraternity", 1980 January 28 (Box 38:, Folder 1551)
  - "Letter to alumni", 1980 January 28 (Box 38:, Folder 1552)
  - "Statement to Appropriations Committee of the General Assembly", 1980 January 28 (Box 38:, Folder 1553)
  - "To members of the community, Black History Month", 1980 February 1 (Box 38:, Folder 1554)
  - "Address at 30th pinning & capping ceremony, Fones School, University of Bridgeport", 1980 February 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1555)
  - "Address to Hartford insurance group", 1980 February 11 (Box 38:, Folder 1556)
  - "Remarks to Joint Committee on Appropriations of the CT General Assembly", 1980 February 21 (Box 38:, Folder 1557)
  - "Remarks to Joint Committee on Appropriations of the CT General Assembly, G.W. Tasker", 1980 February 21 (Box 38:, Folder 1558)
  - "Remarks at Dempsey Hospital dinner", 1980 February 25 (Box 38:, Folder 1559)
  - "Message to Little International Livestock and Horse Show", 1980 February 29 (Box 38:, Folder 1560)
  - "Message to Little International Management Council, Groton, CT", 1980 March 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1561)
  - "Remarks to Joint Committee on Appropriations of the General Assembly re tuition", 1980 March 10 (Box 38:, Folder 1562)
  - "Remarks to the Exchange Club of Danielson, the impact of higher education on local business and industry", 1980 March 18 (Box 38:, Folder 1563)
  - "Dr. Morris S. Dunn Memorial lecture, New Britain General Hospital", 1980 March 19 (Box 38:, Folder 1564)
  - "Testimony on Bill #5384, closing of Torrington", 1980 March 19 (Box 38:, Folder 1565)
  - "Higher education, substance vs. structure", 1980 April 1 (Box 38:, Folder 1566)
  - "Institute of Material Sciences talk", 1980 April 2 (Box 38:, Folder 1567)
  - "Engineering Honors Society, notes for speech", 1980 April 10 (Box 38:, Folder 1568)
  - "Arthur E. Schwarting Pharmacy Practice Symposium, welcoming remarks", 1980 April 16 (Box 38:, Folder 1569)
  - "Remarks to the University community, convocation", 1980 April 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1570)
  - "Remarks at Lincoln performance", 1980 April 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1571)
  - "Remarks at N.E. Deans of Engineering and Technology", 1980 May 2 (Box 38:, Folder 1572)
  - "Address to American College of Dentists", 1980 May 7 (Box 38:, Folder 1573)
  - "Health Science Cluster Program lecture", 1980 May 7 (Box 38:, Folder 1574)
  - "Challenges of the eighties, general remarks", 1980 May 13 (Box 38:, Folder 1575)
  - "Remarks, Change Magazine", 1980 May 13 (Box 38:, Folder 1576)
  - "Remarks at Honors Ceremony, School of Dental and Oral Surgery, Columbia University", 1980 May 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1577)
  - "Address to National Honor Society", 1980 May 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1578)
  - "Commencement, Law School", 1980 May 17 (Box 38:, Folder 1579)
  - "Commencement, UConn", 1980 May 18 (Box 38:, Folder 1580)
  - "Letter to international students", 1980 May 21 (Box 38:, Folder 1581)
  - "Remarks at CT Conference of Independent Colleges, spring meeting", 1980 May 21 (Box 38:, Folder 1582)
  - "Challenges of the 80's for higher education, Farmington Exchange Club", 1980 May 22 (Box 38:, Folder 1583)
  - "Commencement address, Northwest Community College", 1980 May 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1584)
  - "Commencement, Health Center", 1980 May 31 (Box 38:, Folder 1585)
  - "Remarks to Eastern Conference for Dental Education", 1980 June 9 (Box 38:, Folder 1586)
  - "Remarks to North Central CT Health Maintenance Organization", 1980 June 11 (Box 38:, Folder 1587)
  - "Northeast Agricultural Economy Council", 1980 June 16 (Box 38:, Folder 1588)
  - "Council of Deans of the American Association of Colleges of Pharmacy", 1980 July 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1589)
  - "American Society of Agricultural Engineers", 1980 August 4 (Box 38:, Folder 1590)
  - "UConn Centennial Convocation, JAD remarks", 1980 September 23 (Box 38:, Folder 1591)
  - "First annual convocation honoring retired members of faculty and staff", 1980 October 5 (Box 38:, Folder 1592)
  - "Athletic recognition, soccer", 1980 October 7 (Box 38:, Folder 1593)
  - "Presentation to the American Dental Hygienists Association", 1980 October 11 (Box 38:, Folder 1594)
  - "The editor of CDC re dining hall visits", 1980 October 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1595)
  - "CT State Grange", 1980 October 16 (Box 38:, Folder 1596)
  - "Dedication of G. Safford Torrey building", 1980 October 18 (Box 38:, Folder 1597)
  - "Day of Pride", 1980 October 26 (Box 38:, Folder 1598)
  - "Father-daughter communion breakfast, Sacred Heart Academy", 1980 November 16 (Box 38:, Folder 1599)
  - "Remarks to International Advisory Council", 1980 December 5 (Box 38:, Folder 1600)
  - "Remarks at N.E. Conference on Higher Education", 1980 December 16 (Box 38:, Folder 1601)
  - "Annual Address to the faculty", 1979 January 11 (Box 38:, Folder 1602)
  - "Problems in health care delivery, UConn response, 20th Century Club", 1979 January 18 (Box 38:, Folder 1603)
  - "Press conference, On the Occasion of being Selected President", 1979 March 27 (Box 38:, Folder 1604)
  - "The Decade Ahead for Higher Education, Stamford Independent Colleges", 1979 May 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1605)
  - "Eleanor Gill testimonial", 1979 May 29 (Box 38:, Folder 1606)
  - "The Decade Ahead, alumni banquet, new library", 1979 June 1 (Box 38:, Folder 1607)
  - "Commencement address, Tunxis Community College", 1979 June 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1608)
  - "The Decade Ahead for Higher Education, Willimantic Country Club", 1979 June 5 (Box 38:, Folder 1609)
  - "How High is Up, Stony Brook graduation", 1979 January 10 (Box 38:, Folder 1610)
  - "Statement re athletic programs", 1979 June 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1611)
  - "On Throwing Out the Baby with the Bath Water, Hartford Hospital graduation", 1979 June 22 (Box 38:, Folder 1612)
  - "Statement re continuation of regional campuses", 1979 June 29 (Box 38:, Folder 1611)
  - "Address on occasion of the dedication of the family practice unit at Middlesex Memorial Hospital", 1979 July 1 (Box 38:, Folder 1612)
  - "Orientation statement to teaching assistants", 1979 July 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1613)
  - "Fire prevention statement", 1979 July 6 (Box 38:, Folder 1614)
  - "The Decade Ahead, New Haven Rotary", 1979 July 31 (Box 38:, Folder 1615)
  - Interview with Karen Williams, University Chronicle, 1979 August 20 (Box 38:, Folder 1616)
  - "Inaugural address", 1979 September 8 (Box 38:, Folder 1617)
  - "Spare Us the Quick Fix", short version of inaugural address, 1979 September 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1618)
  - "Address to UConn Foundation", 1979 September 20 (Box 38:, Folder 1619)